<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="au.com.langdale.cimtoole.feature"
      label="CIMTool"
      version="1.1.7"
      provider-name="Langdale Consultants">

   <description url="http://cimtool.org">
      CIMTool is an open source tool for supporting Common Information Model (CIM) standards used in the electric power industry.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      CIMTool is copyright 2005,2006,2007,2008 
Langdale Consultants Pty Ltd
Suite 14 7 Narabang Way
Belrose NSW
AUSTRALIA
   </copyright>

   <license>
      This software is Copyright 2005,2006,2007,2008 Langdale Consultants
except where otherwise stated. Langdale Consultants can be contacted at:

http://www.langdale.com.au/contacts

Redistributions must reproduce the above copyright notice, this
list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

This software is provided for evaluation purposes only. Creation
of derived works is prohibited. Sale of the software is prohibited. 

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="CIMTool Update Site" url="http://files.cimtool.org"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="au.com.langdale.cimtoole"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
